<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Essays on Parea</title>
    <link>/essays/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Essays on Parea</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 10:06:22 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/essays/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How user-centered design can produce a winner in the bike &amp; scooter wars (Bird, Lime, Ofo, etc.)</title>
      <link>/essays/user-centered-design-scooters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 10:06:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/essays/user-centered-design-scooters/</guid>
      <description>As Published on Medium
Today’s multimodal fleet companies (e-Scooters, e-Bikes and pedal bikes)are expanding at an astonishing rate. Hundreds of millions of venture dollars have flowed into the market, driven by some investors hoping for a repeat of their ride-sharing wins, while others fear missing out on the next multi-billion dollar companies. These fleets can already be found in many cities across the world as we’re seeing the second wave of transportation competition to change the way humanity moves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Staking is More Useful Than You Think</title>
      <link>/essays/crypto-staking-is-more-useful-than-you-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 22:32:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/essays/crypto-staking-is-more-useful-than-you-think/</guid>
      <description>As published on Token Foundry&amp;rsquo;s Medium
Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus mechanisms are a highly controversial topic in the crypto ecosystem as Ethereum is implementing Casper and many consumer tokens rely on staking economic incentive structures. However, while staking may be a new and relatively untested blockchain consensus mechanism, it has been widely used as an economic mechanism for centuries. This article will examine such cases and explain what staking is, how it works, and why it’s a crucial tool in token design and incentive structures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get Involved in the Cryptocurrency Space</title>
      <link>/essays/how-to-get-involved-in-the-crypto-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 22:32:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/essays/how-to-get-involved-in-the-crypto-space/</guid>
      <description>As published on Medium
Okay, so you’re someone who has recently developed an obsession over the potential of blockchain technology. You’ve invested in a couple of coins, you routinely keep up with the news, and you might’ve even joined a few telegram discussions.
You may have thought to yourself, “Man, so many people are taking advantage of this new space! People of all different backgrounds are starting podcasts, Youtube channels, creating content, taking on new jobs; how can I do my version of that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vinchain Token Analysis</title>
      <link>/essays/vinchain-token-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 22:32:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/essays/vinchain-token-analysis/</guid>
      <description>As published on Medium
VinChain, an ERC20 token whose ICO ended on April 15th, 2018, promises to deliver a “100% trustworthy vehicle history on the blockchain” along with a spate of other non-blockchain features such as an app, vehicle performance analysis, more relevant advertisements, and, of course, a concoction of big data, machine learning, and artificial intelligence. It raised more than 12.5K ETH, equivalent to ~$9m at today’s ETH valuation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The impact of Bitcoin’s deflationary token economics on its viability as a global digital currency</title>
      <link>/essays/the-impact-of-bitcoins-deflationary-token-economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 22:32:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/essays/the-impact-of-bitcoins-deflationary-token-economics/</guid>
      <description>As published on Medium
Bitcoin was created by Satoshi Nakamoto to be a peer-to-peer electronic cash system which would allow online payments to be sent directly from one party to another without going through a financial institution. It emerged in the middle of the Great Recession; as individuals lost their homes and savings, banks and businesses were going bankrupt, and the government was printing money to stimulate the economy through multiple rounds of Quantitative Easing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why No One Should Trust the Weiss Cryptocurrency Ratings</title>
      <link>/essays/why-no-one-should-trust-the-weiss-cryptocurrency-ratings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 22:51:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/essays/why-no-one-should-trust-the-weiss-cryptocurrency-ratings/</guid>
      <description>As published on Medium
Weiss Ratings are on the receiving end of severe crypto community backlash after releasing their Weiss Cryptocurrency Ratings. It’s an ambitious task, for sure, to attempt to rate cryptocurrencies as current conditions make it akin to rating penny stocks — anything can happen. However, it is also a dangerous task. Not for them, of course, but for the consumers, investors, and institutions that will pay for their “research” and use it to inform their investment decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Blockchain Back to the Bare Basics</title>
      <link>/essays/bringing-blockchain-back-to-the-bare-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 22:32:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/essays/bringing-blockchain-back-to-the-bare-basics/</guid>
      <description>As published on Medium
Cause without the underlying technology, this market wouldn’t exist Parea is a collective of technologists, developers, inventors, and investors who write about the crypto market and build upon the blockchain technology. We will post thought essays and discussions about blockchain from the many different perspectives it entails; analyses of the underlying technologies, behavioral economics, market psychology, etc.
The Current State of the Crypto Market Over the last several months, the crypto market has degenerated into a speculative mania nightmare.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>